SETU XOLILIZWE

CONTACT INFORMATION

Email

setuxolilizwe@gmail.com

Phone Number

0781622073

Alternative Phone Number

0616556349

Location

Cape Town

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Valid SA ID

Yes

Date of Birth

12 December 1993

Gender

Female

Race

African

Disability

None

Criminal Record

No

Language

English, IsiXhosa

Valid Drivers License

SKILLS

Soft Skills

Adaptable, Communication

Hard Skills

Cashier, ICT, Technical Support

MY PROFILE STATEMENT

I am highly dedicated graduate in information technology (software development) from Walter Sisulu University. I am well equipped with technology tools and knowledge hence I am proficient in most computer programs such as Microsoft 365. I am highly ambitious and willing to learn, grow and succeed by fair and ethical means. I am seeking an entry level position to enhance my skills and knowledge. I have more than 2 years of experience as an IT technician and I am available anytime.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Walter Sisulu University

National Diploma and Advanced certificates February 2014 - November 2017

Tutor Ndamase SSS

Grade 12 (National Senior Certificate) and national (vocational) Cert. level 4 - 2011

WORK EXPERIENCE

Eastern Cape Department of Education

IT Technician

April 2022 - March 2024

Job Description

Setup workstation with computers and necessary peripheral devices.

Responding to support request and completing job card.

Troubleshooting hardware and software issues.

Installing and maintaining hardware and computer peripherals.

Installing and upgrading operating system and computer software.

Troubleshooting networking and connection issues.

Assist with Anti-Virus Remediation.

Setup departmental emails.

Resolving transversal systems issues.

Reason for leaving

Contract ended

Eastern Cape Department of Education

IT Technician (ETDP SETA Intern)

December 2021 - March 2022

Job Description

Setup workstation with computers and necessary peripheral devices.

Responding to support request and completing job card.

Troubleshooting hardware and software issues.

Installing and maintaining hardware and computer peripherals.

Installing and upgrading operating system and computer software.

Troubleshooting networking and connection issues.

Assist with Anti-Virus Remediation.

Setup departmental emails.

Resolving transversal system issues.

Reason for leaving

Contract ended

REFERENCES

Tandeka Tile

Eastern Cape Department of Education

Tandeka.Tile@ecdoe.gov.za

0662299752

Asanda **Mahanjana**

Stop Discount Furnishers btw@sdfstores.co.za 0603836088

Precious Chiyangwa

Walter Sisulu University pqoche@wsu.ac.za 0437095469

WORK EXPERIENCE

Stop Discount Furnishers

Cashier

September 2019 - November 2021

Job Description

Responsible for cash, debit, credit.

Accepts payments from customers.

Processing sales transactions.

Reconcile cash drawers and sales receipts

Reason for leaving

Moved to another job